<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EverGreen Events</string>
    <string name="enjoy_an_experience_created_just_for_you">Enjoy an experience created just for you</string>
    <string name="evergreen_events">EverGreen Events</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="Timeless_terrace_detail">This outdoor venue features a spacious stone terrace with elegant wrought iron furnishings and cascading flower beds, creating a serene atmosphere for weddings or sunset receptions. Soft string lights and lanterns illuminate the area at dusk, enhancing its romantic ambiance. Ideal for intimate gatherings or sophisticated cocktail parties, the Timeless Terrace provides a picturesque backdrop for memorable moments under open skies.</string>
    <string name="Prime_pavilion_detail">The Prime Pavilion is a modern architectural marvel situated within a lush urban park. Its sleek design incorporates glass walls that seamlessly merge indoor and outdoor spaces, providing panoramic views of landscaped gardens and tranquil ponds. Inside, the pavilion boasts a versatile layout with state-of-the-art audiovisual capabilities, making it ideal for corporate conferences, gala dinners, or product launches.</string>
    <string name="Harmony_halls_detail">Harmony Halls comprises a series of interconnected ballrooms and salons adorned with ornate chandeliers, intricate moldings, and polished hardwood floors. Each hall exudes timeless charm and grandeur, offering flexible configurations for weddings, banquets, or cultural events. The venue\'s classic architecture and opulent decor are complemented by modern amenities, including a bridal suite, cocktail lounge, and culinary team specializing in fine dining experiences. Perfect for hosting large celebrations or formal receptions, Harmony Halls provides an unforgettable backdrop for elegant affairs.</string>
    <string name="Steller_space_detail">Stellar Space is a cutting-edge event venue nestled within a bustling cityscape. Featuring floor-to-ceiling windows and a contemporary design palette of glass, steel, and concrete, this versatile space offers panoramic city views and natural light throughout the day. The venue\'s modular layout includes a main hall suitable for conferences or fashion shows, complemented by breakout rooms and a rooftop terrace for networking sessions or cocktail receptions.</string>
    <string name="Ball_room_detail">The Ball Room is a regal setting steeped in history and elegance, characterized by soaring ceilings, crystal chandeliers, and intricately carved wood paneling. Located within a historic hotel or palace, this grand space evokes a bygone era of opulence and refinement. The venue accommodates large-scale events such as gala dinners, charity balls, or wedding receptions, with a dedicated dance floor and stage for live entertainment.</string>
    <string name="Villa_detail">The Villa features spacious living areas adorned with antique furnishings, a gourmet kitchen for culinary experiences, and multiple guest suites for overnight accommodations. Outdoor amenities include a poolside terrace, pergola-covered dining area, and panoramic vistas ideal for weddings, family reunions, or corporate retreats. Personalized concierge services and a dedicated villa manager ensure a bespoke and unforgettable stay in this idyllic setting.</string>
</resources>